Do it
[music]
Sai Ram Invest friends nowadays it is
difficult to even mention the name of literature and it
is against it
Ajay
9th Nirbhay who is clear in the name of Sai, you
must subscribe to him I trust him, I am
looted as you have written, my
company is still running, my full
duty is going on so my first time is a
little less, that's why I bring videos to
others, some of my
members
go out of my group and make negative comments like this and
make videos in court, what are you wasting time, that's why
I come a little less,
I just saw a couple of places, a
lot of tips, comments in my private, people should
subscribe, I have
a multi writer infotech in my A tag,
others do multi many times and make money by recruiting,
this is my presentation, you guys see it, do
you like it, do you want a database
or don't get emotional, I follow Nandi ji,
say that I
follow Lord Ram, then there is no point in subscribing to those who say
that this is a multibagger, he will make pots
290 crore Billu Billu is ₹2,
a ₹10 Facebook, ₹10 decisions, means now
its price was till ₹10 Facebook, that is why
forget about it, ₹2, that means this company has increased to 75%, so
this Martin Way's
promoter holding is not visible, so
far it is
good, it is running now, show it, got
a spinner appointed in which there is nothing good to show,
who do you need to see me, loot
flour 3.22 12 sugar loan, could not hide it for 5 years
and set 60%, do
not go and appoint it for just ₹5, then you could have come,
operating profit is very troublesome, your
pleasure is 14% maintained, profit
swift text subscribe,
PS4 is worth money,
empty photo is money,
peel it for you, in March 2009, 2286,
today he has reached Bigg Boss,
till now the
result of 121 has not come, it will decrease even more
Depreciation is increasing
or Aishwarya is decreasing from behind, were there
such injuries like that, Pacific decreases,
that history was Rs. 21 at this time, today it has become only
four paise, the purpose of subscribing to this is to get
people to subscribe,
Voice of 100 crore, it means to
sell goods worth two thousand crores, it is understood that it will make
you earn money from holidays, the
accused are the
management and started a drama,
this guest who came from last year,
they have taken 10 decisions, that is,
loot money, share it with the members, so right now the
Aa share,
from land acquisition to promoter
holding of the public, this channel was not subscribed properly,
that is why it was not used, that means the accused have one
eighth share, it is a tremendous way,
not only lid impatient and subscribe to consider, keep the sales,
see the result, operating point was
1000 well, Aa was not
appointed, right now it had reduced a little in between,
okay, so the rest of the profit tax,
cooperative profit margin, we have like this, ten
percent, half an inch less  1234 crores are
decreasing due to decoration, see the interest on internet is
decreasing day by day in Chhattisgarh,
text net profit from Gaya is as much as blind, everyone
subscribe, the sum of money is not
subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe and subscribe, the
more Kabir will increase, its
answer will increase, hungry 167 rupees
current price 500 to 1000 ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company
subscribe once, that is why
subscribe, subscribe button holding
that prostate's companies and mode free company
gives service at daily point profit growth 23.75, subscribe from home, so okay, right,
operating profit margin is
empty, in March 21, his operating profit margin decreased a bit, he is a fakir,
he has been maintaining for 18 years
that his daughter has 450 crores respect and authority,
despite not even being operative, if these
more Itiyathok, right now the student is filling his stomach,
net profit is being made continuously, if
YouTube school then subscribe for this,
March 2010, two thousand subscribe,
March-2010 subscribe, clearly clearly clearly clearly,
clearly subscribe button,
and 1000
a flying  This festival in exchange for the forks,
your children can sit comfortably in it and take the full money,
okay profit posts 158 254
is the full money,
okay, net profit is one forks
Musaddas went, gave a thousand times the money,
apart from this it has become Rs.32
that 12%, today's day is
not done by friends, want to have some knowledge of fundamentals,
till date no one is searching for appointed ghr ghr
running and subscribe,
subscribe and you will meet in the
next video,
that is why there is no need, you will meet in the next video,
friends stay tuned, it has happened,
friends subscribe to my channel, I will
bring such tips, I will also read it,
if like YouTube, ghr ghr, this company
owner, company owner, you will
fall into the subscribe to, do not do it, goodbye, see you in the
next video